I'm very pleased to have joining me for a God's Honest Conversation, Amanda Seals.
Thanks for having me, Charles.
My first question is if you feel as if you've disappeared.
If not disappeared, been silenced. Is that the case?
Disappeared.
I got a podcast. I got the syndicated radio show, The Amanda Seals Show.
I'm on this internet saying what need to be said all the goddamn time.
And I've been strutting through the nation's capital in a pink suit.
For the past how many weeks? How could you miss me?
You seem to get crucified for every little thing in the media. Why do you think that is?
I think there are many reasons.
More reasons than the kangos I wore in the early 2000s.
More reasons than Nick Cannon has mouths to feed.
More reasons than Trump has legal fees. Am I right?
More reasons than white people who got their butts thrown in the river during Fade to Water in Montgomery, Alabama.
But I'm going to focus on the people who support me and subscribe to my Patreon.
TheAmandaverse.com. It's a universe of Amanda.
Okay. You know, we need you to be the superhero that saves democracy.
Are you willing to be that superhero?
Charlamagne, I'm a black woman. I've been a superhero all my life.
Call me Super Seals.
I don't know who's included in that, y'all. But it might be as easy as that security guard in Montgomery throwing his cap in the air.
Bad signal. My milkshake will bring all the voters to the yard. That's why I wear pink. You know, like strawberry.
My milkshake brings all the boys to the yard.
I want to know who's the real president of this country. Is it Joe Biden or Joe Biden?
Hey, Charlamagne, I'm sorry to cut you off, but this has to be the last question for Mrs. Seals.
They're acting like they can't hit me.
Oh, I can hear you. But the real question is, who are the real ones that are going to watch my political comedy doc, In Amanda We Trust?
August 18th at InAmandaWeTrust.com.
I mean, I didn't fake run for office and blow dry this afro for nothing.
The wheels on the bus go around and see you there.
In AmandaWeTrust.com.
Well, that was fun.